what if I told you that you could
choose your favorite season to live
in the rest of your
life what season would you
choose now I know you're saying pastor
that's not even possible but I need you
to check this out see right now you may
be going through a pretty bad season in
life things around you are falling
listen carefully things around you are
falling seems like everything is going
wrong like you may have been that person
that built your house upon the sand and
you're watching it crumble before your
eyes you used to be on fire for God and
now that fire is
gone that relationship that you had that
you thought was going to work out that
that home that
job everything seems to be falling apart
and you may be asking yourself where is
God all that you see before you is this
Stark cold
reality but I want to share something
with you be encouraged because Summer
always comes what is summer summer is
where God sets you on fire summer is
where God moves you out of that bad
season That season of fall That season
of winter summer is where the fire
Returns the question is how do you get
to Summer you have to experience
Springtime see let me explain when Adam
and Eve Sinn I want you to imagine what
it must have felt like as they saw that
first Leaf fall from the
tree imagine how they must have felt
realizing that their sin had brought in
death and destruction and that all they
had to look forward to was the cold
reality of the
grave but beloved
Jesus did not leave us to that cold
grave he did not leave us to our fall
season Jesus came down to this earth he
took our fall upon himself he bore that
fall to the grave and 3 days later he
sprang forth from the Earth to bring
newness of
life it is because of his death burial
and resurrection that we can leave the
fall and winter seasons of our lives and
move into Springtime and ultimately
summer see if you want to move from your
winter and fall Seasons into the seasons
that God has designed for your life you
have to allow Jesus to Spring forth and
what that means is that self Must Die
the Bible says except a kernel of wheat
fall into the ground and die it abideth
alone but if it die it brings forth much
fruit what that text is telling us is
that self must be totally submitted to
the will and to the word of God and when
you allow self to die Jesus Springs
forth in your place so don't get me
wrong this does not mean that your
winter season goes away listen Daniel
lived through a winter season Noah lived
through a winter season Joseph lived
through a winter season all these men
and more fac discouraging times but
because they had Jesus in their hearts
because they had the spring season in
their hearts it did not matter what was
happening around them the trials and
persecution that they faced did not
matter because their Springtime was in
the
heart so I want to encourage
you don't live helplessly in your winter
or your
fall experience the
springtime and choose your season
[Music]